http://www.consolenergy.com/privacy-policy

Loading data...
Privacy Policy
CONSOL Energy and its affiliates (collectively, "Company") is committed to protecting the privacy of certain data that is collected from you and that you submit when you access this web site or web sites under our operation and control (collectively, the "Site").
Please review this policy carefully. The Company reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time, in which event the Site will contain a notice of the change. Changes will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site. By accessing the Site, you are indicating your agreement to the Company's privacy policy.
The Company may ask you to provide information about yourself, or your companies, in order to better serve you, for instance, in connection with an application for employment. Examples of information requested may include name, title, company, address, phone number, email address, and other relevant data. If you decide to provide personal information to the Company on a Contact Form, in no case will Company sell, license or transmit that information to third parties, except as required or permitted by law. Contact Forms are used only to deliver requested information and respond to your questions.
The Company may compile statistical information concerning the usage of the Site. This information allows the Company to monitor its utilization and continuously improve its quality. Examples of this information would include, but not be limited to, the number of visitors to the Site, or to sections or pages within the Site, patterns of traffic flowing through the Site, length of time spent on the Site, or in sections or pages of the Site, the other sites that refer visitors to the Site, the pages of the Site that visitors frequently use as entry and exit points, utilization of the browser and operating systems and versions used by visitors to the Site, etc.
In order to compile this information, Company may collect and store your IP address, your operating system version, your browser version, the pages you visit within the Site, the length of time you spend on pages within the Site, the site from which you linked to ours, search terms you used in search engines which resulted in you linking to the Site, etc.
The Company may use web site "cookies" in the process of compiling the statistical information mentioned above and to tailor certain pages of the Site for your browsing convenience. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies, but our Site may not function correctly if you do. Refer to the Help feature of your browser for information on disabling cookies.
The Site is not directed to children. Company does not knowingly collect any personal information from children. If you are concerned about your child's use of the Site, you may use web-filtering technology to supervise or limit access to the Site.
This Privacy Policy is governed by the internal substantive laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, without regard to its conflict of laws principles. Jurisdiction for any claims arising under or out of this Privacy Policy shall lie exclusively with the state and federal courts within the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania. If any provision of this Privacy Policy is found to be invalid by a court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of this Privacy Policy, which shall remain in full force and effect.
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL COMPANY HAVE ANY LIABILITY WHATSOEVER FOR ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN INFORMATION ON THE SITE, OR FOR ANY DAMAGES, LOSSES, OR EXPENSES THAT MAY OCCUR WHILE ACCESSING THE SITE, OR ANY LINKED SITE, OR THE INABILITY TO ACCESS THESE SITES; OR ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS OR LINE OR SYSTEM FAILURE; OR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT OR SPECIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THE BREACH OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR USE OF THIS SITE, HOWEVER OCCASIONED.
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy, contact the Company at corporatecommunications@consolenergy.com.
Code Of Business Conduct and Ethics
Download the PDF Document
Corporate Governance Guidelines
Download the PDF Document
Charter of the Compensation Committee of the Board of Directors
Download the PDF Document
Charter of the Health, Safety and Environmental Committee of the Board of Directors
Download the PDF Document
Charter of the Nominating and Corporate Governance Committee of the Board of Directors
© 2020 CONSOL Energy Inc. / All rights reserved.
